[BILLY] You have a lot to explain, Abi.
How did you get your hands
on our LoveFeast concept?
[ABI] Your concept?
Don't take what's mine, Ms. Billy.
[BILLY] You messed with
the wrong person.
And I will make sure you face
the consequences.
Girls, I'm so sorry.
I know it's the weekend.
But we need to have a meeting tomorrow.
[YANI] This will be my best series yet.
We'll make a lot of sales.
What's in that?
A lot of things.
Even the list of investors is in here.
Billy said I was a thief.
But she's the original thief herself!
I'll find something I can use
against this woman.
[PRECIOUS]
Maybe you should stay away from her.
[BILLY] If we let it slide,
then she'll do it again.
She messed with the wrong person.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS, THEN FADES]
[SOFT FOOTSTEPS]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy…
Hi!
Sorry, I woke you up.
[BILLY SIGHS]
Can I crash beside you tonight?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- No.
- What do you mean, "no"?
- No, no! No, no, no, no!
- No choice! Slide over!
[WHINING] Not allowed!
- And why am I not allowed here?
- Come on, Billy!
- Because…
- What?
- Because…?
- Just because.
- Let's share the bed, okay?
- No…
- All right, back to sleep.
Good night!
- Good night.
- [ANNOYED] Good night.
[GIGGLES]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[DISTANT BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BILLY] Oliver?
I'm sorry, I can't be with you right now.
I promise, I'll make it up to you.
Next time, we'll go together.
Okay, Billy.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry, Billy.
You can leave him to me.
- Hello!
- Uh…
Sir, we're here for the boxing class.
His name's Oliver Cariño.
You came right on time, ma'am.
The class is about to begin.
- Let's go, Oliver.
- Okay.
Precious?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Brandon?
Wow.
What a coincidence.
[SOFTLY] Yeah.
It's really nice to meet you.
At last.
[FLASH DRIVE CLICKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
Ms. Camille! [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I just called to let you know
that I've already made a list
of potential investors
so LoveFeast can move forward.
I was thinking maybe we should
reach out to them
as soon as possible.
Still working on the weekend?
Well, same here.
We're very much alike in that sense.
And I like it.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
That's just how I am, Ms. Camille.
Especially when I really love my job.
Well, keep it up.
Yes. I promise.
Abi, you're really something else.
I'm impressed.
Honestly, I should thank you.
For being the only one who appreciates me.
Thank you.
Just stay in Pebblng, all right?
Don't ever go back to Billy.
What? Absolutely not!
I'm not going back there.
I don't like her.
I'll never leave.
I'm yours.
Only yours.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
Mr. and Mrs. Chan-Li of Chan-Li Couture
were very responsive.
They said they were willing
to set up a meeting with us.
Same with Ms. Grace of the House of Gems.
We just need to give them
something worth their investment.
Something like LoveFeast?
Bigger and better.
Mmm, wait. How about
a shopping spree kind of date?
[BILLY] Charm, that's not sustainable.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What if…
I feature LoveListers in my vlog?
Not LoveList-centric.
[MARJ] Chief, how about this?
What if we offer a honeymoon package?
[CHARM] Mmm!
It'll come out wrong if it's not
attached to the wedding package,
- which Pebblng stole from us.
- [PHONE RINGS]
I'm sorry.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It'll look like we're just pushing for sex
rather than finding
the right one at the right time.
[PHONE RINGS]
Look.
They don't own the wedding gimmick.
- We just really need a great idea.
- [PHONE RINGS]
- And we need to focus.
- [RINGING CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES BRAZEN]
Toni.
Would you like to answer that first?
Girls, look.
I know it's the weekend
and you're working.
Thank you.
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let's just regroup on Monday.
But please make sure
you have better ideas on the table.
Thank you.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[CHARM] Hey.
Didn't you tell Yani
you can't go to his exhibit?
I said I'd be there later.
Our chief is already frustrated, Toni.
Yeah.
I wonder how we can possibly help.
Geez, she's on the verge of snapping.
And when she's angry, things get ugly.
[VALERIE SCOFFS]
I know, right?
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CHARM SIGHS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude.
Hey.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
What are you doing here?
It's the weekend.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PICTURE FRAME THUDS]
[MARIELA] It's Saturday.
Where are you going?
My boss is asking me to come to work.
Like I told you, Ma, I'll be like Abi.
I'll be someone great.
I'll be someone successful
whom everyone admires.
I'm almost there.
Just wait.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Coach, have them warm up first.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Okay, guys.
- It's destiny, isn't it?
- [COACH] Six, five, four.
- Huh?
- Three, two, go.
That you enrolled your child here.
In our messages,
you said you adopted two kids.
Ah, yes.
Oliver and his older sister, Billy.
Billy is the CEO of LoveList.
- Wow! I should thank her.
- [SOFT LAUGH]
Uh…
So you teach children?
Does that mean you're good with kids?
Like, you're patient with them?
Well, I love kids.
I'm the eldest of ten stubborn siblings.
I help take care of them.
I also help with their education.
Is that why you never got to marry?
Single.
- And ready to--
- [LAUGHS]
They're waiting for you. Look!
Uh, all right, but can you join me?
- Huh? Oh, no, no, no.
- Will that be okay?
- Come on, Precious.
- I don't know how.
It won't take long, it's just the warm-up.
Look, we're lacking one participant.
Come on. It's just the warm-up.
This will be quick.
- Okay, okay.
- Huh?
- Yes. Okay.
- Thank you, thank you!
So is everyone okay now? Let's start?
Okay, so what's important in boxing
is to give and take.
Okay? Okay, all right. Face your partner.
- Boxing stance.
- [PRECIOUS] Shh, shh, shh!
Put your hands up first like this, yes.
Okay, we'll do it first.
Boxing stance, okay?
Jab…
then straight.
Okay? Again, jab and straight.
Okay? For the next one,
we'll go forward and backward.
Forward…
then backward.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[SOFT PUNCHES LANDING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Her friends' accounts are also locked.
I assume those are troll accounts.
Maybe she did that
just in case you check her socials.
I can't let this pass anymore, Jordan.
I remember this.
She said she owns an internet cafe.
But is that true?
She could be lying.
Then I'll visit the place!
- So we can be sure.
- Uh, Chief.
I'll do it. I volunteer.
Me too! I'll come.
Count me in!
- [ADMIRING GASP]
- How do I look?
Wow!
You're so pretty! You've become more--
more beautiful, Ms. Camille!
Thank you.
Anyway…
What are the basis of your assumptions
that they're interested in investing
in a dating company like ours?
It's pretty basic, Ms. Camille.
All of those businesses
will benefit from LoveFeast.
Fashion. Beauty and wellness. Self-care.
Like Ms. Lindsay's skincare brand.
Okay. Set up a meeting with them ASAP.
And tell Morrie first thing by Monday to
draft the proposal and send it right away.
Ah! Yes, I'll do that immediately. Noted!
What are you waiting for?
Try on those clothes.
Ms. Camille?
These? These are all mine?
- Thank-- Thank you…
- Abi.
You're working for me now.
You're representing Pebblng.
I can't have you looking like that.
You must look the part.
And, honestly…
The only thing I like about this
are your shoes.
So, go. Try those on.
Yes. Thank you.
Ah.
[HANGERS RATTLE]
Your bag.
Um…
- Ms. Camille?
- Hm?
Uh, if it's not too much to ask, could I…
ask for a salary advance?
I'm really behind on my bills.
And my mother…
She has a checkup later today.
[ABI INHALES, HESITATES]
I know I'm being shameless right now,
but I'm really tight on budget.
But it's fine if not.
I'm fine, Ms. Camille.
You shouldn't be worrying
about my problems, right?
I was just kidding. I'll try these on now.
Okay.
Eh? It's closed now.
Hey! But the computers are still here.
[CHARM] Uh, wait, let's call them.
- Hello, Ms. Tere?
- Hello, Abi!
I'll pay off my debts to you.
I'll open my internet cafe again.
I'll pay my debts in full,
so wait for me, okay?
You'll pay? You got money now?
I don't believe you.
I told you, I have money!
And my computers aren't yours yet,
so just wait there 'cause
I'm taking them all back, okay?
I'm on my way. Wait for me.
Okay.
- [LINE RINGING]
- Ah, hello?
We'd like to inquire about
the Click Station internet cafe.
- Is this shop Abi's?
- Yeah! That's Abi's!
Hello?
How's it going? Did you find it?
Yes, but it's closed now.
[CHARM] It's closed only because
she has debts to the landlady.
The landlady's holding
all her computer units.
But the landlady said Abi's going to pay
and take back the shop and her computers.
She won't take anything back.
What?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, Oliver, last five seconds!
Five, four, three, two, one!
That's awesome!
Good job, kids. Let's resume
in our next session, okay?
Thank you and see you!
- Okay? Bye!
- Bye!
Your form's good!
I've actually been watching
some tutorial videos.
Oh, that explains it.
Uh, do you maybe want to grab a bite?
- Yes!
- Oh!
- We do, we do!
- [SOFT LAUGH]
- You?
- We do, yes.
We do, right, Auntie?
- Okay…
- We'll go!
- [GIGGLES]
- All right.
[OLIVER GIGGLING]
Sir Eric!
- Hello!
- Oh, Oliver, who are you with?
[OLIVER] I'm with my auntie.
Auntie, this is Sir Eric.
Oh, Sir Eric!
- Nice to finally meet you.
- [OLIVER GIGGLES]
- Oh, nice to meet--
- Brandon, sir.
Oh, Sir Eric, you're quite
popular in our circle!
- Oliver always talks about you!
- [OLIVER LAUGHS]
Uh…
Sir Eric, are you here with someone?
If it's okay, can I sit with you?
[WHISPERS] My auntie's on a date--
- Hey! Shh!
- Oops…
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Sure, go ahead.
[PRECIOUS CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
- Be-- behave yourself.
- I will.
Thank you.
[OLIVER GIGGLES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Here.
- Here's your water.
- [THUDS]
- Thank you!
- The waiters are busy.
- They are. [LAUGHS]
- Let's eat.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm taking a video of Auntie!
Are men banned in Angels of Grace?
[CHUCKLES] Not really.
If they're a relative, it's okay.
But staying there
is exclusively for women.
Oh, so…
does that mean I'm welcome
to pay you a visit?
[PRECIOUS LAUGHS] I said
it's just for relatives.
Ah…
Maybe as a future husband.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
- Psst!
- [WHISPERS] Oh!
[GIGGLES]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you think he's fit to be
a father figure to me?
Are you still looking for a father?
Of course!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[OLIVER LAUGHS]
Caloy, I was able to get some money
to pay Ms. Tere.
I'll be able to open
my internet cafe again.
Huh? You're opening
your internet cafe again?
Don't you have a job already?
Seriously? Being a mere employee
won't make me rich.
Plus, didn't I tell you?
I need to surpass Billy.
All right.
Who's going to look after your shop, then?
- Tell me.
- I'll hire someone.
Why hire someone else
when I'm here anyway?
Are you nuts?
I told you, we can't meet, right--
- Don't leave anything behind.
- Hey!
- Make sure you got everything.
- Hey, those are mine!
Where are you taking my computers?!
Oh! Ms. Tere sold them to us!
She sold them? She can't do that!
I just talked to her just now!
I told her I'd settle my debts with her,
so those computers are mine!
It's too late. We've already bought them.
- Yes.
- [ABI] What?!
W--wait a second.
Marj, Charm, Toni, you…
What are you doing here?
How did you find this place?
Okay, we'll tell you.
But first, tell us this.
How did you get our files on LoveFeast?
- Mm-hmm.
- LoveFeast?
- [CHARM] Yes.
- Stole?
- [ABI] Me? I stole it?
- Yes.
- [CHARM] Mm-hmm.
- Huh?
What are you on? I didn't steal anything!
[ABI] Ms. Billy is too much.
She thinks that I stole it?
I didn't!
Don't just falsely accuse me!
False accusation?
Not at all!
We just really needed them
for a donation drive.
Yes, that's right!
We're going to donate them.
- Oh, for a donation.
- Yes!
Uh, give them back. Here.
Here. Here's my donation, money.
Take it. Give me my computers back.
No, thanks.
Huh?!
This is 40,000 pesos! It's a huge amount!
Sorry, it's not for sale!
- Yes, sorry!
- Sorry.
Well then, let's go, girls.
We might run late.
Not for sale, huh?
- [SHRIEKS]
- Hey, let go of her!
- That was 40,000 pesos!
- I told you, let go of her!
[ABI GRUNTS]
- Here, quick!
- Hey!
- Hey, what the hell?!
- Hold her!
- Ow!
- [ABI] Hey!
[ABI] My shoe-- Those are mine!
- [ABI] Help!
- Those are ours!
- [ABI] Those are mine!
- [TONI] Let's go! A crowd is forming!
- Let's go!
- [CHARM GRUNTS]
- [ABI GROANS] Ow!
- Come on!
Let's go! They're here!
[ABI] Help!
Hey! Hey, those computers are mine!
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING, BANGING CAR]
- Help! Please help me!
- Those are my computers!
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[ABI] Hey! Give them back!
- They're mine!
- [ENGINE REVVING]
Those are my computers!
Ugh!
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS]
[EXHALES]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [HORN HONKING IN DISTANCE]
[CHARM] Oh, man, it got crazy, but…
mission accomplished!
[ALL CHEERING]
You know, it was a good thing
that you thought of
- buying her computers.
- Mm-hmm.
She was absolutely infuriated!
Toni…
What happened to you? Are you okay?
Oh, it's nothing.
What Abi got was worse!
- You should have seen her face!
- [LAUGHTER]
Yes, it was wild!
Like she was gonna bite us off!
- [GROWLS]
- Oh, it's nothing!
That will teach her.
Let's see if she can pull
something like that again.
[TONI] Plus, we didn't just get
her computers.
Yes!
- Ta-da!
- These, too!
[LAUGHTER]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
'Bi. What happened to you?
What happened to your feet?
I'm fine. [SNIFFLES]
Where are your computers?
What? Where'd they go?
They're all gone! All of them!
[ABI BREATHES DEEPLY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Auntie Pres, this is really mine.
Mine is exactly like this.
The brand name is fading,
and it has a scratch here.
That means that Abi is really dangerous!
Be careful!
She even pretended
to be your fan just to rob you!
She did all that just for an idea
and a pair of shoes.
Just let her try doing that again.
I'm not going to back down.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BILLY] Auntie Pres…
- [PRECIOUS] Yeah?
- You're all smiles here!
- So giddy!
- Who's this? That man you're with.
- Ah. That's Sir Eric.
But, apparently, you faked
your police clearance?
This is the original!
I really need a job.
[LUCY] You'll have to look
elsewhere. You're fired!
- Oliver…
- Is Sir Eric here?
[ENRICO] I need to make
it up to my kids.
[CALOY] I love you this much.
You are permanently etched
onto my heart.
Want me to get your shoes back? Huh?
Get my computers too
while you're at it.
If only Ms. Tere hadn't
sold them to Billy.
[BILLY] And now that
the company is facing challenges,
is it right for them to be casualties
just to cut our losses?
[CAMILLE] Because the original idea
came from the newest member
of the Pebblng family.
Oh, ma'am, thank you so much.
- Cheers!
You need this.
I missed this.
[BILLY] Thank you.
- [BILLY LAUGHS]
- Cheers.
You make it look so easy.
Being strong.
Composed.
I could say the same to you.
We got this.
We do.